本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：装汁的容器    Soomii    红豆包    Iz
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第九集
■
挖苦游戏  现在开始
Okay. Burn unit, commence.
你先来
You go first.
我踢足球是因为我忘了我还有手
Oh, I play soccer, 'cause I forgot I have hands.
挖到了
Burn!
我上新闻了  因为我有一颗大脑袋
I'm on the news, because I have a huge head.
挖到了
Burn!
我可跑不过除草机
I can't outrun a lawnmower
杀人
除草
因为我的裙子太紧了
'cause my dress is so tight.
哎呀  我挂了
Oh! I'm dead.
挖到了
Burn.
看  演班卓呢
Whoa. It's Banjo.
我是牛仔  我有...
Oh, I'm a cowboy, and I got...
等一下  先不玩挖苦游戏了
Wait, wait, wait... Suspend burn unit.
这部电影很精彩的
This is a great movie.
是意大利拍的美国西部片
It's a Spaghetti Western,
拍得最好的一部  却没几个人赏识
the best one, underappreciated.
他手里总有一把班卓琴
He plays a Banjo.
我又不瞎
Yeah, I can see that.
他们做了一大堆班卓琴呢
And they made a whole bunch of these.
老爸  家里有比这玩意儿大的东西吗
Dad. Do we have anything bigger than this?
吉恩  你要干什么
Oh, Gene, what'd you do?
目前还没打算  未雨绸缪而已
Nothing, yet. Just planning ahead.
你俩在看什么
What are you guys watching?
没看什么  快回去睡觉
Nothing. Go back to bed.
"挖苦游戏"只有我和老爸才能玩
The burn unit is just me and dad.
子弹是从他的班卓琴里射出来的吗
Whoa! Did he just shoot bullets out of his Banjo?
-是啊  -好给力
- Yes. - Damn!
哎呦  你喜欢啊  吉恩
Oh, you like that, Gene?
可是我们要换台了哦
'Cause we're changing the channel.
别啊别啊  咱一起看会儿
No, no. Let's watch it.
这块儿正好是刚开始
This is pretty much the beginning.
-什么  -吉恩  坐这里  -什么
- What? - Gene, sit here. - What!
你个死胖子  怎么跟沙发一样难推
It's like pushing a couch off the couch!
来  拿着我的搋子
Here. Hold my plunger.
我们真是太激动了
We are just so thrilled
您选了我们家作为承办晚宴的餐馆
that you chose us to cater the event.
老妈  老妈  给我倒上
Mom, mom, fill me up.
-希望我们能够达到去年晚宴的水准  -妈
- I just hope we can live up to last year's event. - Mom...
-那个柯琳・卡维罗  -老妈
- That Colleen Caviello, - Mom...
她确实办得很出色
she really outdid herself,
让人永生难忘呢
and never lets anyone forget about it.
给这只小的倒
Just fill up the little mug.
好好好
Right, right, right.
没问题  福旺德老师
Okay, Mr. Frond.
再见  再见
Goodbye. Goodbye.
我们要准备什么样的食物啊
So what are we catering?
你都夸下海口了
That sounded promising.
这场晚宴非常重要  鲍鲍
Oh, it's a real big deal, Bobby.
这实际上是给
It's a fund-raiser
蒂娜的"解决冲突俱乐部"募集资金
for Tina's conflict resolution club.
柯琳・卡维罗去年负责食品供应
Colleen Caviello made the food last year.
她今年可以负责...  吹气球
This year she can go... blow a balloon.
好耶  你要给我们的募捐晚宴提供食物喽
Yeah! You're catering our fund-raiser.
不错嘛  我们能得多少啊
That's great. How much does it pay?
-一分不得  -一分不得
- Nothing. - Nothing?
这是场慈善晚宴  鲍鲍
It's a benefit, Bobby.
-食物以意面为主  -可我们家不做意面
- It's a spaghetti dinner. - But we don't make spaghetti.
这可是全校募捐晚宴  鲍勃
This is school fund-raising, Bob.
主角一向是意面
It's a pasta game.
要么做意面  要么滚回家
You make spaghetti, or you go home.
而且  我们这是做好事呢
Besides, it's for a good cause.
是啊  为了盖过柯琳・卡维罗的风头
Oh, yeah... to one-up Colleen Caviello.
的确  的确是件"好事"
That's a, that's a great cause.
你是没看着  鲍勃
You weren't there, Bob!
那场面都气死人了
You don't know how awful it was.
真好吃啊
This is delicious.
俺滴个神
Oh, my God!
这通心粉的味道真赞
I love this ziti.
他们在赞我做的通心粉
They love my ziti.
那是我这辈子最悲惨的一天
And that was the worst day of my life.
反正我这么做不是为了跟柯琳攀比
Anyway, this isn't about Colleen,
而是为了蒂娜
this is about Tina.
我们正在筹资购买防弹垃圾箱
We're raising money to buy a bulletproof trash can
这样黑帮分子最后就会缴械投降了
so gang members can finally throw out their guns.
我们俱乐部还教授解决冲突的技巧
And we're teaching conflict resolution skills,
这个非常实用哦
you can use in your own lives.
没错  蒂娜
That's right, Tina,
福旺德老师管理这个俱乐部
Mr. Frond is running the whole thing.
福旺德老师
Ugh, Mr. Frond?
他可真是风流...  涕淌
He's a tall drink of... annoying.
这话不假
That may be true,
不过你得把他淌出来的鼻涕喝下去  先生
but you're gonna drink that drink, mister.
我才不要
I don't want to.
我费尽心机弄到手承办这次晚宴的机会
I have worked too hard to get us this event,
所以你得对福旺德老师友好点
so you'll be nice to Frond,
还得给我做意面和肉丸
and you'll make spaghetti and meatballs!
-不介  -听话  -不介  -听话
-No. -Yes. -No. -Yes.
那好吧  可我是不会好好干活滴
Fine, but I'm gonna half-ass it.
老爸  你快看
Dad, check it out.
小公主吉他
Little princess guitar.
吉恩  那是我的
Gene, that's mine!
你从来都没用过
You never use it.
我就像那班卓
I'm like Banjo.
那个坏蛋叫啥来着
What's the bad guy's name?
-瑟维奇  -瑟维奇  没错
- Ceviche. - Ceviche, yeah.
他让我想起一个同学  楚楚
He reminds me of this kid at school, Choo-Choo.
-楚楚  -没错  算是我的死对头吧
- Choo-Choo? - Yeah. He's kind of my Nemesis.
如果我在讲笑话
If I'm telling a joke,
他就会提前把笑点爆出来
he'll say the punch line before I do.
一个吸血鬼走进酒吧  说
A vampire walks into a bar and says,
-给我来杯  -给我来杯"淡血"
- I'll have a... - I'll have a blood lite.
淡血:  同名恐怖故事集
有个西佬长了一只橡皮脚趾
What do you call a Spanish guy
你要叫他什么
with a rubber toe?
-罗伯托  -罗伯
- Roberto! - Rober...
什么蜜蜂会产奶
What kind of bees make milk?
-初母峰  -初母峰
- Boo-bees! - Boo-bees!
Boo-bees:  初为人母的女性的双峰
所以  我要用这把吉他
So, I'm gonna use this guitar
去回击楚楚  就想班卓那样
to stand up to Choo-Choo like Banjo.
很...  很不错嘛  吉恩
That's, uh... that's great, Gene.
但是我觉得你的表情不对劲
But I think your face is wrong.
我的表情不对劲
My face is wrong?!
你应该使出班卓那冰冷犀利的眼神
Yeah, you should do the Banjo icy stare.
像这样吗
Like this?
不  不对
No. Not like that.
不不不
No, no, no.
别学狗叫
Don't growl. That...
是这样吗
Like this?
这个倒可以试试
Maybe try that.
楚楚害怕中风病人吗
Is Choo-Choo scared of stroke victims?
害怕极了
Terrified.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
吉恩  吉恩
Hey, Gene, Gene.
你有什么好辩解的
How do you plead?
我是无辜的
I'm innocent.
凶器上全都是你的指纹
Your fingerprints were all over the murder weapon.
可我没有手指
I don't have fingers.
法官大人
Your honor!
我没时间瞎胡闹
I don't have time for this.
什么  你没时间玩"食物法庭"
What?! You don't have time for food court?
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
来听听极品段子
Hey. Wanna hear a good one?
什么东西绿颜色  会唱歌
What's green and sings?
-来啊  说啊  -埃...
- Go ahead. Do it. - El...
埃尔维斯...
Elvis...
埃尔维斯・帕...
Elvis Par...
我不玩了
Forget it.
我来告诉你什么东西绿颜色会唱歌
I'll tell you what's green and sings...
埃尔维斯・帕斯利
Elvis Parsley.
冷笑话:  把猫王Elvis Presley的姓氏换成Parsley(香菜)
就变成了"会唱歌的香菜"了  (￣￣")
不许你再抖别人段子的包袱
You don't say the punch lines to other people's jokes anymore.
给我记住喽  便便
You got that, Poo-Poo?
这他妈怎么回事
What the hell?
多谢  多谢
Thank you. Thank you.
多谢各位捧场  多谢
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
好了  吉恩  来看
Anyway... Gene, look.
法庭就要做出最后判决了
They're about to announce the verdict.
罪名成立
Guilty.
不
No!
把他带下去
Take him away.
吉恩  你要去哪
Gene, where are you going?
吉恩怎么了
What's up with Gene?
我不知道  千层面
I don't know, Lasagna.
我不知道
I don't know.
知道吗  煮意面根本算不上是煮食物
You know, cooking spaghetti isn't even cooking.
充其量是在烧开水
It's just, like, boiling water.
老鲍  晚宴我能参加吗
Hey, Bobby, can I come to this thing?
我看不妥吧
Uh, I don't think so.
怎么不妥了
Why not?
这里有些妈妈已经离婚了 对吧
Some of these moms are divorced, right?
她们认识认识我
They meet me,
我再认识认识她们的孩子
I meet their kids.
也许还会传几个球玩玩
Maybe throw the ball around.
不是里面的那个球  是...
Not inside, but...
ball还有"睾丸"的意思
我们说好的
Uh, we agreed
不许你再参加学校活动  泰迪
no more school events for you, Teddy.
-老爸  你猜怎么着  -怎么着
- Hey, dad. Guess what? - What?
我像班卓一样  把楚楚打得落花流水
I acted like Banjo and took Choo-Choo down.
所有人都笑了
Everyone laughed.
什么呀  就一个人笑了
Well, one kid laughed.
彼得・派斯卡德罗
Peter Pescadero.
还是个智障
He has a learning disability.
没错  但是他懂我的笑点
Yeah, but he knows what's funny.
既然你已经出了这口恶气
Now that you stood up for yourself,
那就恭喜你一下  吉恩
oh, congratulations, Gene...
这事就此打住成吗
can we stop talking about it?
好了老爸  我提议  今晚
Okay, tonight, I propose,
等其他人都睡下后  尤其是吉恩
dad, that after everyone else goes to bed, Gene...
我们就开始玩挖苦游戏
we fire up the burn unit
然后看《狗狗犯罪团》
and we watch Canine Criminals,
然后看柔术表演
and then that stretching show,
也许再看会儿西语配音的《甲壳虫汁》
and then maybe a little Beetlejuice in Espanol.
蒂姆・波顿1988年的作品
甲壳虫汁  甲壳虫汁  甲壳虫汁
Beetlejugo. Beetlejugo. Beetlejugo.
我也很想这样玩
I would,
但是你这宇宙超级无敌模范好老爸
except a certain best dad in the world
今儿买了这个回来
went out and got this!
班卓系列全集
It's the complete Banjo box set!
十二张影碟
All 12 DVDs
外加超过二十八小时的特别收录
and over 28 hours of extras.
二十八小时
28 hours?!
老爸  那把叉子能给我看看吗
Dad, can I... see that fork for a minute?
给
Um... here.
谢了  我只是想...
Thank you. And I just want to...
不
No!
马上就是最精彩的部分了  吉恩
Best part right here, Gene.
我的手指就动两下
There's only gonna be two shots,
第一下干掉你
me shooting you,
第二下干掉这杯威士忌
and then me drinking this shot of whiskey.
这台词太妙了
Wow. Oh, what a line.
看吧看吧  尽情看你们的傻缺电影吧
Go ahead, watch your stupid movie.
这儿又不是没有人跟我玩
There are other people for me to hang out with around here.
蒂娜  起来  我们去玩吧
Tina, get up. Let's hang out.
好啊  我们可以练习一下解决冲突的方法
Okay. Maybe we can practice conflict resolution.
对我说些刻薄话  让我练习练习保持冷静
Say something mean to me so I can not react.
说什么都行吗
Anything I want?
对
Yeah.
你的房间看起来
Well, uh, your room looks like
像是变态赛马师装饰的
it was decorated by a perverted jockey.
你这样说的时候
When you say that,
我就会感到  你是想伤害我的感情
what I feel is that you're trying to hurt my feelings.
神啊  你语速为什么这么慢
Oh, my God. Why do you talk so slow?
你这样说的时候
When you say that,
-我就会感到  -我勒个去  蒂娜
- what I feel is that you're trying to hurt... - Oh man, Tina.
这真是太太太无聊了
This is really, really boring.
好吧
Okay, well...
老妈  想不想出去玩
Hey, mom, you want to hang out?
想呀想呀
Oh, I'd love that!
母女互动时间
Oh, mother-daughter bonding time.
就像我和我妈当年一样
Just like me and my mother.
先来化个妆
Ooh! Makeover!
好了  牛仔仔们
Okay, my little cowpokes.
该上学了
Time for school.
剩下的可以今晚看
You can watch the rest tonight.
老妈  你怎么能这样
Mom, How could you?!
我哪样了
How could I what?
你怎么能鼓励他们这样
How could you encourage this?
露易丝  别捣乱了
Oh, Louise, don't be a pill.
他们俩正在享受父子互动时间
A little father-son bonding is going on here
多么美好啊
and that's a good thing.
他们俩可不总是如此融洽
These two don't always do it so well.
铃鼓独奏
Tambourine solo!
哎呀我去
Sheesh.
好了  看我给你示范回旋球的投法
All right, this is how you throw a spiral.
准备好了吗  看球
You ready? Here comes a bullet.
该死的橄榄球
Oh, stupid ball!
没有带子才会这样的
It's 'cause there's no laces.
我好饿
I'm hungry.
好吧  今天就到这儿  进去吧
All right, we're done. Go inside.
我要吃花生酱
I want peanut butter!
看来我们在看电影时更有共同语言
It turns out we bond better over movies
在看我喜欢的电影时
that I like to watch,
在我把吉恩拉过来看我喜欢的电影时
that I make Gene watch.
没错
Yeah.
真是  真是太感人了
Oh, that's... that's adorable.
我要去上学了
I'm going to school.
-好  -很好
- Good. - Great.
祝你学有所成  然后去当律师
Why don't you learn something and become a lawyer.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
"调心击"控制法
调整情绪  心怀歉意  击掌庆祝
A.B.S.
这种解决冲突的方法
The conflict resolution program
正在我校广为使用
sweeping our school.
你们已经学会了我这套体系
You all know my system,
然后在意面晚宴上
and at the spaghetti dinner,
你们的家长或法定监护人也将学会这套体系
so will your parents or legal guardians.
贝琪  我这么说是因为你妈妈在坐牢
Um, Becky, 'cause your mom's in jail.
蒂娜  乔丝玲  小吉米  我们开始排练吧
Tina, Jocelyn, Jimmy Jr.... let's rehearse.
贝琪  你看着就行了
Becky, you just watch.
蒂娜刚刚得知她的死党乔丝玲
Tina here just found out that her best friend Jocelyn
跟小吉米说自己是个怪咖
told Jimmy Jr. that Tina is "whack".
开始吧
And... acting.
蒂娜  乔丝玲跟我说你是个怪咖
Tina, Jocelyn told me you are whack.
乔丝玲  你个丑八怪  我恨你
Jocelyn, you skank. I hate you.
随便你怎么说
Whatever.
我说的可是事实
It's true.
你就是个怪咖
You are whack.
停
And... freeze!
这种方式可解决不了问题
Well, that resolved nothing.
我们倒回去重来  好吗
Let's rewind, shall we?
现在我们来试试"调心击"控制法
Let's work out our A.B.S.
调  调整情绪
A! Access your feelings!
你在小吉米面前说我坏话
When you gossiped about me to Jimmy Jr.,
很伤我感情的
it hurt my feelings.
心  心怀歉意
B! Be apologetic!
对不起
Sorry.
击  击掌庆祝
S! Slap it!
干得漂亮  晚宴时这样做就行了
Well done. Do it just like that at the dinner.
同学们  去吃午饭吧
Oh, enjoy your lunch, everyone.
如果你在练习之外
If you ever gossip about me to Jimmy Jr.
跟小吉米说我坏话
outside of a conflict resolution skit,
你就等着吃拳头吧
I'll punch you in the face.
我们只是在排练啊  蒂娜
It was just a skit, Tina.
我真的会揍人的
I will punch you.
揍死你  揍死你  揍死你  揍死你
Again and again and again and again...
天哪  真是个神经病
My God, what a psycho.
揍死你  揍死你  揍死你  揍死你
And again and again and again and again and...
重要的是
Well, the important thing is,
我和吉恩一起看了这部电影
I shared this movie with Gene
这让他在学校里扬眉吐气了
and it helped him stand up for himself at school.
我像吉恩那么大的时候
Eh, I beat up a lot of kids like Gene
可是揍了不少他那样的臭小子
when I was his age.
我并不是恃强凌弱
Not that I was a bully...
只是像吉恩这样的臭小子  需要吃点教训
just kids like Gene, you know, that get beat up.
鲍勃  肉丸做的怎么样了
Bob, how are the meatballs coming?
要美美无瑕的哦
Because they need to be perfect.
跟你的汉堡一个样  都是球形的
Hey, it's just like your burgers, only spherical!
-手拿开  -怎么啦
- Hey! - Hey, what?
这些不是给你吃的
They're not for you.
这些是用来在慈善晚宴上
They're for me to show off
在其他妈妈面前炫耀的
in front of the other moms at the fund-raiser.
鲍鲍  为柯琳・卡维罗
Bobby, make one extra-big
做一个超大号的  噎死她
for Colleen Caviello to choke on.
好的
Okay.
成  看来今天只好和你们坐一起了
All right, looks like I'm sitting with you today.
我来定定规矩
Here's the pecking order:
我为先  其次  你俩随意了
Me, then either of you.
这两张贴纸你比较喜欢哪个
Which sticker do you like better,
我的紫色瓢虫还是苏西的红色瓢虫
my purple ladybug or Susie's red one?
拜拜您呐
And good-bye.
喂  吐吐
Hey there, Spew-Spew.
在这儿见到你真有趣
Funny seeing you here.
午餐时间你也不放过我
In the cafeteria during lunch?
没错
Yeah.
你干嘛老这样
Why do you keep doing that?
老怎么样
Keep doing what?
真是个怪胎
You're weird!
怪胎  你觉得你想说的是"反传统主角"
Weird? I think you mean anti-hero.
看我帽子
Look at the hat.
那是妈妈的遮阳帽  你这呆瓜
It's mom's sun hat, you dork.
你喜欢抖我的包袱吗
You like finishing my jokes?
先吃完我的剩饭吧
Well, finish my food.
吉恩  你这样简直是个出色的地痞流氓
Gene, you are being a class act jerk.
这些段子都是你那本傻缺的笑话书里的
This is all about jokes from your stupid joke book.
休想再羞辱我的《纯爷们笑话精选》
You've insulted Jokes for Blokes for the last time.
别做梦了  吉恩
Oh, don't you even think about it, Gene.
食物大战
Food fight!
"调心击"控制法
调整情绪  心怀歉意  击掌庆祝
不
No...!
鲍勃  这俩小家伙互砸东西
And these two, Bob, were throwing at each other.
我恨你
I hate you.
我才恨你
他们似乎有矛盾
They seem to be in conflict.
我相信我们可以和平解决
I'm sure we can, uh, work through it.
我想让你看看我的"调心击"控制法
I'd like you to take a look at my A.B.S.
不了  多谢
Um, no thank you.
给他看看"调心击"控制法  福旺德老师
Show him your A.B.S., Mr. Frond.
-我们都想看看"调心击"控制法  -好
- We'd all like to see your A.B.S. - Okay.
我真不想
I really don't.
-你说过好几次了  -吉恩
- And your ding-dong. - Gene.
吉恩  当露易丝跟你发火时
Gene, why don't you access
你为什么不调整一下情绪
how it makes you feel that Louise's angry with you.
好吧
Fine.
我就说这么多
That's all I'm gonna say.
我也说这么多
Well, this is all I'm gonna say.
看打
Hi-yah!
放开我的...
Let go of my...
露易丝  露易丝  露易丝
Hey, Louise, Louise, Louise.
你没用到"调心击"控制法
You're not using your A.B.S.
真二
Um, this is dumb.
-鲍勃  -哎
- Bo-- Bob. - Yes.
当你说"真二"时
When you say "This is dumb,"
我真的很想掐你的眼睛
it makes me feel like pinching you in the eye.
你这是干嘛
Why did you do that?
这样我们就可以解决问题
So we can resolve this
给你的孩子们竖立好榜样
and set a good example for your children.
那好吧
Okay.
那我就踹你小腿
I will now kick you in the shin.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
好了
All right.
不要用记忆压抑的艾米丽砸人
Don't throw repressed memory Emily!
她不会记住这个的
She won't remember this.
这招真的很管用  福旺德老师
Well, this is really working out, Mr. Frond.
您的体系棒极了
Your system is amazing.
-我们要回去了  -不不不不不
- We're gonna go. - Ho. No, no, no, no, no.
知道吗  我忘了说
You know what? I forgot to say...
留堂  给我留堂
Detention! Detention!
还有你
And you,
我要取消你的资格
I am gonna cut you!
我要取消你参加
I am gonna cut you
解决冲突意面晚宴的资格
out of the conflict resolution spaghetti dinner!
得了吧  你不能...
Wha-- Oh, come on, you can't...
太晚了
Too late!
解决冲突意面晚宴
The conflict resolution spaghetti dinner
现在变成解决冲突禁食晚宴
will now be a conflict resolution fast.
事情进展得不是很顺利啊
Well, that didn't go so well.
他看起来很生气
Yeah, he seemed angry.
摆什么臭架子
Frothy.
还傲慢自大  是不
And kind of bloated, right?
也许他是脱水了
Maybe he's dehydrated.
你们老妈会杀了我的
Your mother's gonna kill me.
很高兴有机会谈妥这个问题
So glad we had a chance to talk this out!
艾米丽  对不起
Emily, I'm sorry!
留堂
Detention?!
还被勒令停办"和平友爱俱乐部"晚宴
And we're banned from catering the peace club dinner!
-鲍鲍  -很抱歉  琳  我
- Bobby! - I'm sorry, Lin, I...
你知道不知道
I can't even tell you
为了举办这次晚宴我欠了多少人情
how many favors I had to call in to cater that thing.
欠了多少
How many?
两个
Two!
蒂娜  你不是应该看店的吗
Tina, you're supposed to be watching the restaurant.
我没心情上菜
I'm too upset to serve food.
你干了什么  你把门锁上了吗
What'd you do? Did you lock up?
-是的  -客人们都被锁在餐馆里了吗
- Yes. - Were there customers inside?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在没人会来参加募捐晚宴了
No one's gonna come to the fund-raiser now.
干得漂亮  鲍鲍
Good job, Bobby!
这不是我的错  琳
It's not my fault, Lin.
是福旺德老师的错
It was Mr. Frond's fault.
-是露易丝的错  -是吉恩的错
- And Louise's. - And Gene's!
罪魁祸首  其实是那部傻缺电影
And most of all, that stupid movie.
别把错怪在电影头上
Hey, don't blame the movie.
别互相埋怨了
Leave bingo out of this!
闭嘴
Shut up!
都给我闭嘴
All of you!
我要把这些影碟锁到我的珠宝屉里
I'm locking these movies in my jewelry drawer.
-别这样  -这不公平
- Aw, come on. - Unfair!
是时候锁起来了
About time.
你反应过激了  琳
You're overreacting, Lin.
就他妈的过激怎么地
The hell I am!
我负责策划一场意面晚宴
I'm in charge of a spaghetti dinner
晚宴上却没有意面
that's not gonna have any spaghetti!
如果我们都运用"调心击"控制法...
If we all just worked on our A.B.S...
现在不是卖弄那种狗屎的时候  蒂娜
Not now with that crap, Tina!
意面晚宴
留校察看
真不敢相信我被留堂了
I can't believe I got detention.
如果我是你
If I were you,
我会教训吉恩一顿
I would teach Gene a lesson
让他永生难忘
he'll never forget.
我的记录一直很完美
I had a perfect record,
-直到你在上面画上了污点  -污点
- and then you tainted it. - Taint.
看来你已经把楚楚置于死地了
Looks like you got Choo-Choo right where you want him.
给他一个冰冷犀利的眼神
Just give him that icy stare
然后拨拉几下琴弦  最后了结他
with some little princess and finish him.
想见识见识这个吗
You want a little of this?
是的是的  他想见识见识
Oh, oh, yeah, he wants it.
现在  用冰冷的眼神杀死他
Now give him the icy stare.
煞煞他的威风
Put him in his place.
你死定了
You're dead!
安静
Quiet!
我去把留堂的吉恩和露易丝接回来
Okay, well, I'm gonna go get Gene and Louise from detention.
很好  带点肉丸去吧
Great! Bring some meatballs.
我们有很多很多的肉丸哦
Got plenty of meatballs.
精心打扮  却无处可去
All dressed up and nowhere to go.
肉丸
Meatball.
好吧
All right.
我要走了
I'm gonna leave.
吉恩  放马过来
Gene, this happens now!
咱们比划什么啊
Uh, how are we doing this?
瞪眼比赛
Staring contest?
还是讲冷笑话
Joke-off?
踢爆他菊花  楚楚
Kick his ass, Choo-Choo!
他们为什么光着膀子  我的天啊
Why are their shirts off? Oh, boy.
我本不想这样的
I didn't want to do this.
我还没有按下蓝色按钮呢
I haven't even pressed the blue button yet.
我甚至不知道那会是什么样的声音...
I don't even know what sound...
打  打  打
Fight! Fight! Fight!
-住手  不许打架  -谢天谢地
- Stop, there's not gonna be a fight. - Oh, thank God.
放开我  我这辆愤怒的火车已经脱轨了
Let me go! This train is off the tracks.
呜  呜
Choo-Choo!
现在我明白你名字是怎么来的了
Oh, I get the name now.
我还以为那是他嚼东西时发出的声音呢
I always thought it was 'cause of how he chewed.
因为他嚼东西的声音很像火车叫唤
'Cause he chews like a train.
冷静点
Hey, calm down.
咱回家吧  吉恩
Let's go home, Gene.
-你敢碰我儿子  -抱歉  什么
- You touching my kid? - Sorry. What?
我说  你敢碰我儿子
I said, you touching my kid?
他刚才在欺负我儿子
Oh, he was attacking my kid.
是么  好极了
Oh, yeah? Good.
你们俩干嘛都光膀子啊
What is going on with the shirts?
我要踢爆你菊花
I'm gonna beat your ass so bad
这样今晚我就不用健身了
I can skip the gym tonight.
老爸  情况不妙啊
Dad, this is bad.
谢谢提醒  露易丝
Thank you, Louise.
都在我掌控范围内呢
I have it under control.
放马过来吧
This happens now!
杀了他
Kill him!
-快跑  -我跑不动
- Run! - I can't.
脖子上挂着这把该死的吉他我跑不动
I've got this frigging guitar around my neck!
-吉恩  往下来点  -我在努力
- Oh, Gene, push down. - I'm trying.
好了
All right.
好了  目前为止我们安全了
All right, just so we're clear,
我们这不是躲避他们
we're not hiding from those guys.
只是礼貌地谢绝他们发出的打架邀请
We're respectfully declining their invitation for a fight,
对吧
okay?
对  不  谢谢你
Right. No, thank you.
刚才那节骨眼要不是你
I would absolutely get into a fight
我就挨他们...
under the right circumstances, if...
什么味儿
What's that smell?
-吉恩  -吉恩
- Oh, Gene! - Gene!
对不起嘛
I'm sorry!
别出声  我听到他们过来了
Hey, shh, shh. I hear them.
他们过来了
They're coming.
真...  你听到了吗
Real...? You-- you hear them?
-骗到你啦  -露易丝  够了
- Gotcha. - Louise, enough.
你煽风点火三整天了
You've been stirring the pot for three days,
像小孩一样不懂事
and acting like a baby.
现在你给你哥惹了麻烦
Now you owe your brother an apology
快跟他道歉
for getting him in trouble.
我道歉
Me?!
你们两个各自欠我一个道歉
Both of you owe me an apology.
我们两个  为什么
Both of us? Why?
就因为我们想看班卓吗
Because we wanted to watch Banjo?
因为你们两个不再陪我玩了
Because you stopped hanging out with me.
-什么  -用假声说话
- What? - Shh. Use your slide voices.
首先  老爸不跟我玩"挖苦游戏"了
First, the burn unit stopped hanging out.
然后  吉恩又不跟我玩"食物法庭"了
Then, the lunch bunch stopped hanging out.
神啊  这帽子给戴的
God, we have lame names.
你们两个不陪我玩
Who the hell am I gonna hang around,
我要跟谁玩
if not you two?
老妈和蒂娜  她们两个"月见红"么
Mom and Tina... the menstruation nation?
那是什么破名字啊
Ugh! That's a really bad name.
你俩是我的仅有
You're all I've got.
露易丝  我很抱歉
Louise, I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉  别哭了
Me, too. Don't cry.
骗到你们了
Ha! Got you.
你们还真以为我在哭呢
You thought I was really crying.
恶心死了
Gross.
吉恩  停下
Gene, stop.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我憋不住啊  都是焦虑惹的祸
I can't help it. It's anxiety.
我还没放完呢
And turkey jerky.
真是太不可思议了
It's so incredible.
-你放的屁闻起来很像我的  -真的么
- Your farts smell like mine. - Really?
好么  你们俩又开始互动了么
Oh, great. Are you guys bonding again?
很抱歉  但这是一个重大发现
I'm sorry, but that's a huge discovery.
屁味跟指纹一样
A fart is like a fingerprint,
我们有相同的指纹
and we have the same fingerprints.
击个掌
High-five.
-来击个掌  -好
- Put your hand up. - All right.
我发誓我的屁味跟你的也一样  老爸
I swear my farts smell like your farts, dad.
我可不觉得  露易丝
I don't think so, Louise.
等等等等
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
怎么样
Huh?
不  闻起来像你老妈的
No. That smells like your mom's.
不要啊
No!
你老妈
Oh, your mom.
你们老妈和蒂娜可怎么办
What are we gonna do about mom and Tina?
她们可以和我们一起住这里
They could live in here with us!
我有个更好的主意
I think I know a better way.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
我要饿死了  真窘迫
I'm starving. How embarrassing.
看来我烤的通心粉又要被热议一整年了
Guess people will be talking about my baked ziti for another year.
琳达  我刚才没看见你
Oh, Linda, I didn't see you.
小柯  你好吗
Hi, Coll. How are you?
谢谢大家
Thank you.
今晚  在你们的帮助下
Tonight, with your help,
我们筹到了一百多块钱
we raised over $100.
其实是一百一十块
It was $110.
我警告过你  丑八怪
I warned you, skank!
姑娘们  注意形象
Girls, please.
这可不是排练时间
It's not time for the skit.
才不是排练呢
This isn't a skit.
我跟她来真格的
This is real life.
去年  唯一引发动乱的
Last year, the only fighting was
就是我的通心粉
to get seconds on my ziti!
够了  柯琳
Okay, that's it, Colleen.
我来告诉你们那通心粉到底是怎么回事吧
Let me tell you about that ziti.
调味汁是在店里买的  你心知肚明
That sauce was store-bought, and you know it.
女士们  别打了
Ladies, please!
我警告过你了  鲍勃
I thought I told you, Bob.
这里不欢迎你和你的意大利面
You and your spaghetti aren't welcome here.
但我想说几句
But I want to say something.
谢谢  不用
No, thank you.
你那些伤人的话我听够了
I've had enough of your hurt speech.
有挽回的余地吗
Would it make a difference if I...
如果我运用"调心击"控制法
worked on my A.B.S.?
我想...
I want to... a--
第一步是什么来着
What was "A" again?
-屁眼  -硝酸戊酯
- Anus. - Amyl nitrate.
调整  我想调整情绪
Access... I want to access my feelings.
好了好了好了好了  够了够了够了够了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, enough, enough, enough, enough.
大家都想杀人了吧
Everyone's about to kill each other here.
咱们...  开吃
Let's... let's eat!
好耶
All right!
肉丸  肉丸
Meatballs! Meatballs!
肉丸在这里
Get your meatballs here.
还有意面
And spaghetti.
来  柯琳  你怎么不把肉丸放脸上
Here, Colleen, why don't you put these balls in your face?
-食物大战  -不不不
- Food fight! - No, no, no...!